[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":43203,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":541248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":12995,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":554247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":28436,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":582686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":5014,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":587703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":19230,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":606935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1478,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":608414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":11502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":619918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1142,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":621062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":625150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1  = 2 bec ause 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1119,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":626270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":629055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":942,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":629998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with t he first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":633102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1397,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":634502,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":637270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1094,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":638365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":644294,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":645286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3262,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":648550,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1071,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":649622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, y ou subtr act 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":652518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1102,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":653622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":25795,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":679421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":88496,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":767918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":774550,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1103,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":775654,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":779503,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1037,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":780542,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the  inverse  of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":783294,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1295,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":784590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":787734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":871,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":788606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":15015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":803622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3215,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":806838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":52367,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":859206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br / ><br />  However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":119591,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":978798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":23565,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1002366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":12199,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1014566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10- 0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1021758,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":30687,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1052446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator  under +< sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":25440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1077888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1675,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1079565,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":9614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1089181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3223,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1092405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions a s accura tely as possible.","rt":45415,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1137821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7431,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1145254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1158,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1146413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4144,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1150558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1157086,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1160566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1165038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2814,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1167854,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. The two numbers are added together and since the result is not 9 or greater we do not subtract 9. ","response_history":["5. You come","5. You comb","5. You com","5. You co","5. Yo","5. Y","5. Aft","5. Af","5. A","5. ","5. The two numbers are added together but sin","5. The two numbers are added together bu","5. The two numbers are added together b","5. The two numbers are added together ","5. The two numbers are added together, bu","5. The two numbers are added together, b","5. The two numbers are added together, ","5. The two numbers are added together,","5. The two numbers are added together and since 5 is not gre","5. The two numbers are added together and since 5 is not gr","5. The two numbers are added together and since 5 is not g","5. The two numbers are adde d togeth er and since 5 is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since  is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since th is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since the is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since the  is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since the re is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since the res is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since the resu is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since the resul is not 9 or greater","5. The two numbers are added together and since the result is not 9 or greaterw","5. The two numbers are added together and since the result is not 9 or greater we do not subtrct","5. The two numbers are added together and since the result is not 9 or greater we do not subtrc","5. The two numbers are added together and since the result is not  9 or gre ater we do not subtr","5. The two numbers are added together and since the result is not 9 or greater we do not subtract 9 ","5. The two numbers are added together and since the result is not 9 or greater we do not subtract 9. "],"rt":88870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1256726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. The result of adding 8 + 4 is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","response_history":["3. The result is 12. Sn","3. The result is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result ois 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result ofis 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subt ract 9 f rom 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of ais 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adis 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of addis 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of addinis 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of addingis 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adding is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adding 8is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adding 8 is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adding 8 +is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adding 8 + is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adding 8 + 4is 12. S ince 12  is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. ","3. The result of adding 8 + 4 is 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3. "],"rt":52287,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1309014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 is the identity under +9 because anything you combine with 0 will result in getting the same thing back. ","response_history":["0 is the identity under +9","0 is the identity under +9 because  anything you a","0 is the identity under +9 because  an","0 is the identity under +9 because  a","0 is the identity under +9 because  ","0 is the identity under +9 because you get th","0 is the identity under +9 because you ","0 is the identity under +9 because you","0 is the identity under +9 because yo","0 is the identity  under + 9 because y","0 is the identity under +9 because ","0 is the identity under +9 because anything you combine with 0 will result in getting the same ti","0 is the identity under +9 because anything you combine with 0 will result in getting the same thing back. "],"rt":164991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1474006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":30022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1504029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1508917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":7487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1516405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the identity. 9-9 = 0. ","response_history":["6/ ","6/","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 0","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result . 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is gre ater tha n 8 we subtract 9 from the result t. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to . 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to g. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to ge. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get t. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get th. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we  subtract  9 from the result to get the . 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the i. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the id. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the ide. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the iden. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the ident. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the identi. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you add 3 and 6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the identit. 9-9 = 0. ","6. When you ad d 3 and  6 you get a result of 9. Since it is greater than 8 we subtract 9 from the result to get the identity. 9-9 = 0. "],"rt":74150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1590558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, you can get number 4, 6, and 8. But there is no way to make numbers 1, 3, 5, and 7. ","response_history":["No. ","Yes. 2+ ","No, you have","No, you hav","No, you ha","No, you h","No, you can get number 4, 6, and 8. But there is no way to make numbers 1, 3, 5 ","No, you can get number 4, 6, and 8. But there is no way to make numbers 1, 3, 5, and 7. "],"rt":324255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1914814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words h ow you g ot your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. You can get numbers 0, 3, 6. But there is no way to get numbers 2, 4, 6, and 8. ","response_history":["No. You e","No. You can get numbers 0 ","No. You can get numbers 0, 3, 6 an","No. You can get numbers 0, 3, 6 a","No. You can get numbers 0, 3, 6 ","No. You can get numbers 0, 3, 6. But there is no way to get numbers 2, 4, 6, and 8 ","No. You can get numbers 0, 3, 6. But there is no way to get numbers 2, 4, 6, and 8. "],"rt":143478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2058293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using successive operations of 5. ","response_history":["No, you can only get number ","No, t","N o, you a re unable to make numbers 1,2,3,4","No, you are unable to make numbers 1","No, you are unable to make numbers 2.3","No, you are unable to make numbers 2.","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7,8,","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7,8","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using +5","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using +","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using ","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using ","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using the results of ","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using the","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using th","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using t","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using succesive o","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using succesive ","No, you are unable to make numb ers 2, 3 , 4, 5, 7, and 8 using succesive","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using succesiv","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using succesi","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using successive operations of +","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using successive operations of ","No, you are unable to make numbers 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 using successive operations of 5. "],"rt":246983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2305278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, and 8 using successive operations of 6. ","response_history":["Np, ","Np,","Np","N","No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, and","No, you are unable to numbers lik e 1, 2,  4, 5, an","No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, a","No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, ","No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, and ","No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, 67, and ","No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, 6,7, and ","No, you are unable to numbers like 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, and 8 using successive operations of 6. "],"rt":128079,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2433358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":23311,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2456670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"0 + n = 0","response_history":["0 + n = 0"],"rt":75791,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2532462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whatever you add to 0 will be n. since n=n you would subtract n to get an identity of 0. ","response_history":["0 is the element that you would combine withh","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity. Sinc","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity. Sin","0 is the element that you would combine with n to  achieve  it's identity. Si","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity. S","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity. ","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity.","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity sin","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity si","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity s","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whateer ","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whateer","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whatee","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whatever you ","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since  whateve r you add to 0 wo","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whatever you add to 0 will be n. since n=n you would subtac","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whatever you add to 0 will be n. since n=n you would subta","0 is the element that you would combine with n to achieve it's identity since whatever you add to 0 will be n. since n=n you would subtract n to get an identity of 0. "],"rt":252020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2784486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure. I wasn't able to come up with an answer for this question. ","response_history":["I'm ","I'm","I'","I'm not  sure. I  wasn't able to come up with an answer for this question. "],"rt":179303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2963790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":60991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":3024782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":27263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":3052046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>,  x must  be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":31087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":3083134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False. if x = 2 and n = 3, then 3/2 leaves a remainder of 1. ","response_history":["True","Tru","Tr","T","False. if x = 2 and n = 3 3","False. if x = 2 and n = 3 ","False. if x = 2 and n = 3, then 3/2 leaves a remainder of 1. "],"rt":441248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":3524383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator u nder +<s ub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":25323,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3549710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Never. If x = 2 and n = 4 then 2 + 2 2. You would not be able to get numbers 1,2, or 3. ","response_history":["ne","n","Nee","Never. 2_ ","Never. 2_","Never. 2 ","Never. 2","Never. ","Never. If x = 2 and n = 2 then 2+","Never. If x = 2 and n = 2 then 2 +2","Never. If x = 2 and n = 2 then 2 + 2 2. You would not be able to get numbe rs 1","N ever. If x = 2 and n = 2 then 2 + 2 2. You would not be able to get numbers 0","Never. If x = 2 and n = 2 then 2 + 2 2. You would not be able to get numbers 1 ","Never. If x = 2 and n = 4 then 2 + 2 2. You would not be able to get numbers 1 ","Never. If x = 2 and n = 4 then 2 + 2 2. You would not be able to get numbers 1,2, or 3. "],"rt":214126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3763838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":34975,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3798814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press  Conti nue to continue.","rt":1719,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3800534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":5472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3806007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3808558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've com pleted?  If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Trigonometry, Statistics. ","response_history":["Trigonometry, Statistics. "],"rt":20676,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3829238,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":21094,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3850334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical  group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":15327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3865662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3870710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definite ly"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3873318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3875583,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2518,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3878102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":5182,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3883286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. But I did use a spreadsheet program. ","response_history":["No. But I did use a spreadsheet program. "],"rt":17375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3900662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Thank you for the chance to participate. ","response_history":["Thank you for the chance to participat. ","Thank you for the chance to participat.","Thank you for the chance to participat","Thank you for the chance to participate. "],"rt":9582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3910246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]